两天前我发现我有癌症
Two days after I found out I had a fatal tumor on my spine,
接着突然出现了一个外科医生
a spinal surgeon fell out of the sky.
我们有一个很好的击败你的计划
We had such a wonderful plan to break you, Jack.
我完美的计划曝光了
My wonderful plan got shot to sunshine
当你看到我的X光片发现我快死了的时候
when you saw my damned x-rays and figured out I was dying.
你想让我救你的命?
You want me to save your life?
我想让你自己想救我的命
I want you to want to save my life.
你考虑一下好吗
All I can ask is that you think about it.
TELL ME YOU LOVE ME AGAIN
BUT THIS TIME
SLOWLY
'CAUSE YOU'RE TALKING TOO FAST
BABY  MUCH TOO FAST
COME ON AND SQUEEZE ME AGAIN
BUT THIS TIME
SLOWLY
'CAUSE I LIKE YOUR GRASP
OH,OH,OH
BUT IT'S MUCH TOO FAST
YOU SAID THAT OUR LOVE WILL GROW TOGETHER
'CAUSE YOU'RE MINE,ALL MINE...
警察  开门
Police. Open the door.
我这里没有什么情况
Everything's all right in here.
女士  我们有证据表明
Ma'am, we have reason to believe
酒店里有很危险的任务
someone extremely dangerous is in the motel.
-我们正在搜查每个房间-屋里只有我一个人  警官
-We're conducting a room-to-room search.-I'm alone, officer.
这个人可能正拿枪指着你
This person could be holding you at gunpoint,
强迫你说只有你一个人  请开门
forcing you to say that. Please open the door.
我不认为我应该开门
I don't think I should.
三秒钟后不开门我就把门撞开
Ma'am, you have three seconds before I break this door down
1...
One...
2...
two...
想兴奋一下吗?
Hey.Wanna get it on?
当然
Hell, yeah.
(警告)
Warning.
你好
Hey.
你也好
Hey yourself.
(警告)
Warning.
你在干什么?
Whatcha doing?
扔石块
Throwing rocks.
(警告)
Warning.
我觉得你应该推那个摇杆
I thought you had to pull the lever.
我知道怎么得到鱼形饼干
I know how to get a damn fish biscuit.
那就给我弄一块
Then get me one
你想让我觉得自己很能干?
What, you trying to keep me feeling productive?
你做了这份验血报告  然后在上面标注符号?
You took these blood tests,made all the notations?
这些X光片是什么时候拍的
How old are the x-rays?
一周前
A week.
从这张片上看你脊柱上的肿瘤有边缘形  不宜动手术
The tumor on your spine is borderline inoperable,
按照肿瘤扩展的速率来看
and at the rate it's growing,
边缘形一个星期就会消失
that borderline goes away in about...one week.
那天那个手术室--设备齐全吗?
The O. R.We were in-- is that fully equipped?
是
Yes.
麻醉药?  消毒剂?
Anesthesia? Sterile?
有
Yes.
你明天就该动手术
You need to be in surgery yesterday.
好  那么
All right, then.
你想要什么都行  我准备好了
Whatever you need,it's yours. I'm ready.
不  我认为你误会我的意思了
No, I think you misunderstood me.
我没有说我会给你动手术
I didn't say I was gonna do it.
我只是想让你知道你会怎么死
I just wanted you to understand how you're gonna die.
你认为我相信你们的人吗?
You think I believe you people?
你认为我信任你吗?
You think I trust you,
相信只要我动了手术
that I'm gonna just do the surgery
然后  希望  你会放我走?
and hope that you let me go?
Jack--
别!
Don't!
好吧  Jack
Well, Jack,
我对你的决定感到很失望
I'm very disappointed in your decision.
是吗  Ben
Well, Ben,
还好你不会失望太长时间
at least you won't have to be disappointed for very long.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译： 小黄 后期：梁良 双语字幕：sealovemoon
你不该来这里
You shouldn't have come here.
嗯  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
我犯了一个错误
I've made a huge mistake.
我现在十分后
I am just full of regret right now.
真的吗?
Seriously.
婚礼之前看到新娘会倒霉的
it's bad luck to see the bride before the wedding.
婚礼前看到新娘
It's bad luck to see the bride
穿着衣服才会倒霉
in her dress before the wedding.
而你呢  没穿衣服
You, my friend, are naked.
你试过了吗?
Have you tried it on?
我要摒住呼吸
I have to hold my breath
才能扣上扣子
to get the claspy things to clasp,
所以还是等到婚礼前几分钟才穿吧
so I'm waiting till the absolute last minute.
还有12个小时了  可能你应该试穿一下了
It's in about 12 hours.You might wanna get clasping.
我知道这...
I know it's...
这太快了
It's been fast
但是...这没有错
but... this is right.
我能感觉到...
I know it's real...
我爱你  Monica
and I love you, Monica.
我也爱你  Kevin
I love you too, Kevin.
来吧  该干活了
Come on. Time for work.
他呢?
What about him?
他今天休假
He's got the day off.
如果他不干活  我也不
Well, if he's not working, neither am I.
-你也不?-去吧  小妞
- Oh, you're not?- Just go, Freckles.
老板想给我一天假
Man wants to give me a day off,
就让他给我一天假
let him give me a day off.
不Sawyer  我们是一个团队
No, Sawyer. We're a team.
你敲碎石块  我运送
You break the rocks, I haul 'em.
好吧  没问题
All right.Fine.
上帝知道我不会拆散团队
Lord knows I wouldn't want to break up the team.
他怎么了?
What happened to him?
应该是被动物袭击了
Must have been an animal,
可能是一只熊
maybe one of the bears.
我们把他抬回去吗?
Are we gonna carry him back?
不  我们就把他埋在这里
No We're gonna bury him here.
是吗?
Are we?
露营地的人...
The people back at camp...
最近经历了太多葬礼
there's just been a few too many funerals lately.
没有人需要看到他这个样子
Nobody needs to see him like this.
我会溜回露营地拿几个铲子
I'll slip back to the beach and get a couple shovels.
-我和你一起去-不  我一小时后回来
I'll come with you.- No, I'll be back in an hour...
一个人走不安全  John
it's not safe to go alone, John.
谢谢你的关心
I appreciate your concern.
到底是什么东西杀了Eko?
So what killed Eko?
露营地的人们管它叫"怪物"
Folks back at the beach call it the "monster."
我不知道那应该叫什么
I don't really have a name for it.
你不相信有怪物
You don't believe in monsters.
我相信我看到的
I believe in what I can see.
很明显你知道那是什么
But obviously, you have.
为什么不告诉我你的看法?
So why don't you tell me what you think it is?
那可能是带我们来这里的东西
It might be what brought us here.
你确定那是怪物?
So you believe that this monster
-所以你认为这个怪物决定了Eko注定要死?-我相信Eko的死是有原因的
decided that Eko was meant to die?-I believe Eko died for a reason.
只是现在我还不知道是什么原因
I just don't know what it is yet.
所以你就说谎吗?
Is that why you lied?
我们不是回露营地对吗  John?
We're not headed back towards the camp,are we, John?
当然是
Sure, we are.
只是需要绕几个道
Just need to take a little detour first.
(围墙被破坏)
Compound breach.
-(围墙被破坏)-她在哪里?
Compound breach.Where is she?
有人在输电网那里  让他趴下  她也是
Someone's on the grid.I want him on the ground, her too.
如果他乱动就开枪
If he moves, you shoot him.
-对  他们在这里-好的
- Yeah, they're here.-- Okay.
医生又出来了?  你确定?
Did the doctor get out again?You sure?
那他知道吗?
Well, does he know?
她是怎么到这里来的
How the hell did she get over here?!
站起来  快  站起来  快跑
Get up! Come on! Get up! Go!
Alex!  Alex!
Alex!Alex!
-你知不知道你在干什么?-怎么?  你会开枪打我吗?
-What the hell do you think you're doing?-What, you gonna shoot me?
你知道你不应该来这里的  现在冷--
You know you're not supposed to be here,so let's just calm...
Danny  你把他怎么样了?  他现在在哪?
what did you do to him, Danny?!Where is he?
我要跟Ben谈谈
I want to talk to Ben.
没问题  这听起来是个好主意
Sure.That sounds like a great idea.
现在我们应该把弹弓放下来--
So why don't we just lower our little sling--
他在哪里!  告诉我!
where is he? Tell me!
-不!  放开我!-带她离开这里
Don't-- no! Get off of me!
-怎么处理她-带她离开!
- What do I do with her?- Get her out of here.
放开我!  听着  他们说的任何话都不能相信
Put me down!Listen, whatever they say,don't believe them.
他们会杀了你的男朋友
They're gonna kill your boyfriend
就像杀了我的男朋友一样
just like they killed mine.
我不明白  应该还有两周的
I don't understand.It's supposed to be two weeks.
-我们的计划提前了-什么?  这是命令吗
-Our schedule's been moved up.- Is that an order?
-是他的计划-真蠢
-It's coming from him.- That's stupid.
不是我说的
It's not my call.
没有办法  Danny
That's the way it is, Danny.
好吧
All right.
你可以带上这个--
I would like for you to put this on
跟我来吗?
and come with me, please.
你认为我会带上一个麻袋
You think I'm gonna put a hood over my head
-就因为你说了一个"请"-不  Kate  我认为你会带上麻袋
'cause you said "please"?
No, I think you're going to put a hood over your head
因为站在我身后的人 在我身后凶神恶煞的那个--
because the man standing behind me,the one who's burning a hole in my back--
他会杀了Sawyer
that man is going to kill Sawyer.
但如果你带上这个跟我来
But if you put this on and you come with me,
你就可以为我们做点事情
there's something you can do for us
并且救他的命
that will save his life.
进来
Come in.
甜心
Oh, sweetheart.
你真美
You're beautiful.
太美了
Absolutely beautiful.
外面怎么样了?
How is it out there?
外面有很大一群兴奋的警察
There are a lot of excited policemen.
别担心  我告诉过他们
Don't worry. I have asked them
当你说"我原意"的时候不准朝天上开枪
not to shoot their guns in the air when you say "I do."
想不到婆婆对人这么好
You know, mothers-in-law aren't supposed to be so nice.
Monica...
我有东西要送给你
I have something for you.
Suzanne  你不应该这样
Suzanne, you shouldn't have.
这是我结婚时我妈妈给我的
My mother gave that to me on my wedding day.
她说有一天我会把这个给我的女儿
She told me someday I'd give it to my daughter,
但我生了四个男孩...
but since I had four boys...
给
here.
太美了
It's perfect.
Kevin第一次来这个教堂的时候
You know,Kevin's been coming to the church here
还只有这么点高
since he was about yea high.
当我第一次看到你的时候  Monica
When I first met you, Monica,
我被你的诚恳和对Kevin的忠诚打动了
I was struck by your honesty and devotion to Kevin.
我问她最爱你哪个地方的时候
And when I asked him what he loved most about you,
他说"所见即所得"
he said,"because what you see is what you get."
好了
That being said,
你们都准备好了戒指
we've got the rings,
也立下了誓言
you've vowed your vows,
现在我宣布你们结为夫妻
and I now pronounce you husband and wife.
抬脚
Watch the Step.
我尊重你们的隐私
I'll give you two some privacy.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的  你呢
Yeah. You?
我...我好极了
Yeah, I'm...I'm great.
他们把你关在哪里?
Where are they keeping you?
外面  一个笼子里
Outside, in a cage.
Sawyer?
他也在笼子里
He's in a cage, too.
他们让我们工作
They're making us work.
工作?  为什么工作?
Work? On what?
我不知道为什么  但很累
I don't know what it is,but it's big.
我们搬运石块--
We're hauling rocks and--
他们伤害你了吗?
Did they hurt you?
Kate
没事的--不会有事的
Hey, it's gonna...it's gonna be all right.
都过去了
It's gonna--
Jack  你必须照办
Jack, you have to do it.
什么?
What?
他们给你说的  动手术
This thing that they told you to do...this operation.
她说如果你不这样  他们就--
She said that if you do it,then that they would...
他们给你说了什么?
What did they do to you?
-他们对你做了什么?-什么都没有
What did they do to you?-Nothing.
-他们是怎么让你来求我的?-JACK  别这样
How did they get you to ask me?-Jack Please
-他们给你什么好处?-什么都没有
What did they offer you?- Nothing.
-那你来这里干什么?-他们要杀了Sawyer!
- Then what are you doing here?They're gonna kill Sawyer!
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起  她说如果你肯动手术
I'm so sorry,but she said that if you do it,
如果你做了  他们很快就会让我们走
and if you do it soon,they'll let us go.
你相信他们?
And you believe them?
我别无选择
I have to.
Jack...
求你了
Please.
我们说完了
We're done here.
Jack
我们说完了
We're done in here!
对不起  Jack
Jack, I'm sorry.
Jack你必须做  他们说他们会
You have to do this.They said that they couldn't--
把她带出来
Get her out of there.
Jack...
求你了  Jack
Jack, please!
你好
Hey, you.
晚餐吃什么  丰盛吗?
Hey, what's for dinner, gorgeous?
玉米面豆卷
It's taco night.
你在做玉米面豆卷
You're making tacos?
是的  你最好喜欢吃
Yes, and you better like 'em.
不然呢
Or what?
不然就没有甜点
Or no dessert.
我要挂了  很快就回家
I'm leaving now. I'll be home soon.
我爱你
Love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
Mars特工
Agent Mars.
是我
It's me.
我很高兴
Well, I'm glad.
今天早上我才发现
I realized this morning
今天是耶稣升天日
that it was the feast of the ascension,
这让我很不爽
and I was feeling bad.
从你上次打电话算起已经过了很多个神圣的节日了
A lot of holy days have come and gone since you last called.
-我觉得我们是朋友-我不想再逃跑了
I thought you and I were friends.I don't want to run anymore.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
他知道你是什么人吗?
Does he know who you are?
Edward  别这样
Edward, please.
我知道你不想
I know you don't want
今后一直追踪我
to spend the rest of your life chasing me
求你了  我爱他  放过我
Please, I love this guy.Just let me go.
告诉你
I'll tell you what.
如果你真的改过了
If you can really stay put,
如果你真的定居了
you really settle down,
我就不在追捕你了
then I'll stop chasing you.
但你知道那不可能
But you and I both know that's not gonna happen.
Sawyer...
你真的关心他吗?
You really care about him, huh?
他在哪里?
Where is he?
我很抱歉你不能帮我们
I'm sorry you weren't able to help us, Kate.
快走  Ford
Move it, Ford.
Danny?
Danny.
-Danny!-混蛋!
Danny.-Son of a bitch!
对不起  Jules
Right. Sorry, Jules.
你有什么想对这个女孩说
You got anything you wanna say to your girl,
最好今晚就说完
you'd best say it tonight.
今天过得怎么样?  宝贝
And how was your day, honey?
舱门爆炸的时候
When the hatch exploded,
你用来祈祷的棒子从书上掉到我面前
your prayer stick fell out of a tree right on top of me.
我和Sayid把它找来
So Sayid and I went out to get it,
因为我们觉得应该把它和你埋在一起
because it didn't feel right to bury you without it.
我认为你的死是有原因的Eko先生
I'd like to think you died for a reason,Mr. Eko.
希望我们不久会知道
Just hope it's not too long before we find out
它到底是什么
what the heck it might be.
安息  Eko先生
Rest in peace, Mr. Eko.
谢谢你帮助我找到我的--
Thank you for helping me find my...
John 擦亮眼睛看北方
我看到Jack了
I saw Jack.
他们带我去见他
They brought me in to see him.
-他们想让他给Ben做手术-Ben是谁?
-They want him to do surgery on Ben.-Who the hell's Ben?
Henry  把我们关进来的人  他病了
Henry, the guy who brought us in.He's sick.
他们说如果他做了  他们就会让我们走
And they say that if he does it,they're gonna let us all go.
-那我们是什么  诱饵?-差不多
And you and me are what,bait?- Somethin' like that.
医生自己知道决定
At least the doc ain't dumb enough to do it.
我告诉他他必须做
I told him he had to.
你为什么做这么傻的事?
Why the hell would you do something so stupid?
-就你的命-我不需要你救我
-To save your life.-My life don't need saving.
你想死?!
You wanna die?!
他们会杀了你
'Cause that's what's gonna happen.
Pickett一直在等机会
Pickett is just waiting for his chance.
我看到他瞪着你
I've seen him look at you.
混蛋  小妞  别动
Damn it, Freckles, stay put.
你知道他会做什么
And you know what he's gonna do.
所以别装作你不在乎
So don't pretend like you don't care.
下来  小妞  我们试过了  这没用
Get down, Freckles!We already been through this.
闭嘴  James
Shut up, James.
你不想Jack救你的命
You don't want Jack to save your life?
那你自己救你的命
Then you're gonna save your own.
我们现在就离开这里
We're getting outta here now.
停下  混蛋  Kate!
Stop it! Damn it, Kate.
走  离开这里  快跑!
Go. Get outta here. Run!
你走出了笼子  你为什么不逃跑  Kate?
You're out of your cage.Why don't you run, Kate?
我--我不逃跑...
'Cause me...I ain't running...
因为我们根本逃不掉
'cause there ain't no place to go.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我们不是在以前的那个岛上
We ain't on our island.
我们在另外一个岛
We're on another island,
就像恶魔岛一样  中间隔了几英里
like Alcatraz,couple miles offshore.
除非你是美人鱼  或者你会游泳
So unless you're a mermaid,or you got a boat,
我们是跑不掉的
there ain't no point.
你之前准备什么时候告诉我这些
When were you planning on telling me this?
不告诉你
Never
为什么?!为什么你要这样?
Why not?!Why wouldn't you?!
因为我想让你觉得
'cause I wanted you to believe
我们还有希望
that we had a damn chance.
这是干什么?
What was that for?
我不知道
I don't know.
真不错
Very nice.
现在轮到你了
Okay, now it's your turn.
看看你桌布下面
Look under your place mat.
你干了什么?
What did you do?
看看就知道了
Just look.
-这是什么? -记得我们的蜜月吗?
What is it?You know that honeymoon
我已经拖了六个月了?
I've been promising you for six months?
你现在手上拿的是两张到哥斯达黎加的机票
You are holding in your hand two tickets to Costa Rica.
准备好你的护照吧  宝贝
So get your passport ready, baby.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
我太爱你了
I just love you so much.
过来
Come here.
我问你点事情  小妞
Let me ask you something.
上次那家伙打我的时候
The day blockhead was beating on me,
你说...
and you said...
"我爱你"
"I love you."
只是为了...让他停止  是吗?
That was just...to get him to stop, right?
我也爱你
I love you, too.
谁在那边?
Who is this?
喂?
Hello?
喂!
去检查一下门
Try it... the door.
想不到这样能促进感情  我也很惊讶
If it helps, I was surprised, too.
如果我是个赌徒
If I were a betting man,
-我会下注把你和她关进去更有可能-闭嘴
-I would have picked her and you.- Shut up!
我想这个东西
Well,I suppose this would be
用来钉我的棺材更合适
the proverbial nail in my coffin,wouldn't it?
明天
Tomorrow.
什么?
Sorry?
明天早上  首先
Tomorrow morning, first thing.
准备好我以前说过的东西--
Get everything I mentioned before,
仪器  麻醉药
the instruments,the anesthesia,
还有一个能拿镊子的人
and someone who can hold a damn clamp.
好
Of course.
我会把它取出来--你的肿瘤
I'll get it out...your tumor,
让你活下去
and I'll keep you alive.
但我要你保证
But I need your word.
你以前承诺我的东西都要给我
I need what you promised me before.
我要离开这个岛
I need to get the hell off this island.
成交
Done.
未怀孕
你在忙什么?
What you working on?
整理一些
Just finishing
从坦帕市逃脱的犯人的资料
some I.R.S on that fugitive recovery out of Tampa.
这就是警察的工作--做不完的文件
That's what being a cop is...just endless paperwork.
谢谢你  甜心
Thank you, sweetie.
其实我也是一个逃犯
What if I told you I was a fugitive?
其实我也在逃
What if I told you I was on the run
我把我的父亲炸死了
for blowing up my father,
你知道这些只是时间问题
and it was only a matter of time before you found out?
这不好笑
This isn't funny.
我没有开玩笑
It's not a joke.
我差点就怀孕了
I almost had a baby, Kev.
我  差点有宝宝
Me. A baby.
我不能再继续了
I can't do this.
玉米面豆卷?  我不会做玉米面豆卷
Taco night?I don't do taco night!
冷静Monica  我的名字不是Monica
Calm down, Monica.My name's not Monica!
我爱你...
I love you...
但我不能留下来了
but I can't stay.
等一下  别走
Wait. Hang on.
Kev...
-我有点不对劲 -我给你下药了
-Something's wrong with me.-I drugged you.
你做了什么?
You what?
我必须这样  不然他们就会认为你知道我是逃犯
I had to.Otherwise, they would think you knew.
而且会问你很多问题
People are gonna be asking a lot of questions,
我不想你失去工作  Kev
and I didn't want you to lose your job. Kev!
这会是个很谨慎的过程
This is gonna be a very tricky procedure.
如果我叫你做什么
If I tell you to do something,
我要你马上就做  不要问问题
I need you to do it then and there,no questions asked.
明白了吗?
Is that understood?
你可能难以相信
You may find this hard to believe,
但我很擅长遵守命令
but I've always been very good at just following orders.
这个回答代表"是"吗?
Is that a yes?
是
Yes.
很好
Good.
开始吧
Let's go.
你会紧张吗...
Do you get nervous...
在做手术之前
before you do surgery?
以前会  现在不了
I used to,but not anymore, no.
不管发生了什么
Whatever happens,
局势都会大变  不是吗?
everything will be very different,won't it?
毫无疑问
No doubt about it.
Juliet...
Alex问过我的情况吗?
did Alex ask about me?
没有  昨晚我们送她回家了
No We took her home last night.
我不知道她现在在哪里
I don't know where she is now.
另一边见
Well, see you on the other side.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
我需要你倒数20秒
I need you to count down from 20.
二十
20...
十九
19...
十...
10…
手术刀
Scalpel.
我们走
Let's go.
Ben才刚刚开始动手术
Ben's just gone into surgery.
Ben是开始把性命交给他们中的一个人
Ben just put his life in the hands of one of them.
Jacob的名单上没有Shephard
Shephard wasn't even on Jacob's list.
-Sawyer Sawyer-看看是谁逃出笼子了
-Sawyer Sawyer-Well, well, well,look who got out of her cage.
你们有机会时应该逃跑的  我们走James
You two should've run when you had the chance.- Let's go, James.
-不  请不要  你们没有必要这么做 -他必须跟我们走
-Don't. Please.-You don't have to do this.He's coming with me,
你不能阻止我们
and you can do anything about it!Step away.
再给他打针止血剂
Give me another hemostat.
擦血
Swab again.
镊子
Clamp.
怎么了  他没事吧?
What happened? Is he okay?
他的血压降低了  我们应该输血吗?
His blood pressure's dropping.Should he be bleeding like that?
不  不  不用
No. No, he shouldn't.
-离桌子远点 -Jack
Back away from the table.-Jack
离桌子远点  马上!
Back away from the table now!
你在那里能听到我吗?
Can you hear me in there?
能
Yeah
很好
Good.
我刚刚在Ben的肾脏旁边切了一个口
I just made a small incision in Ben's kidney sack.
如果我一个小时之内不把他缝上  --
Now if I don't stitch that back up in the next hour,
他就会死
he's dead.
把对讲机那进来!
Now get in here and bring that walkie-talkie!
-闪开 -不
-Step away!-No
你动手  我就杀了她
You let go, or I do her, too.
-放手 -别放手
-Let go!-Don't you let go!
别放手  打他
Don't even think about it, Sawyer.You fight!
不!  不! Sawyer!
No No Sawyer
不!  别这样
No Don't
不!
No
求你了  Sawyer
Sawyer, please!
别碰他
You get your hands off of him!
跪下!
Down on your knees!
别!
Please!
要我做什么都行
I'll do anything you want!
我要你看着
I want you to watch.
闭上眼睛  小妞
Close your eyes, Freckles.
站起来
Stand up.
闭上眼睛!
Close your eyes!
别放弃!
Don't you give up!
不!  不!
No No
不!
NO!
这一枪是为了Colleen  你这个狗娘养的
This is for Colleen,you son of a bitch!
不
No
Danny  听到了吗?  快接
Danny, are you there?Pick it up.
快接!
Pick it up, Danny
听到了!  什么事!
I'm here! What?!
你在笼子附近吗?
You anywhere near the cages?
没错
Yeah, you could say that.
把对讲机给Kate
Give your walkie to Kate.
为什么我要这样做?!
Now why the hell would I do that?!
因为如果你不这样做
Because if you don't,
医生就会让Ben死
the doctor's gonna let Ben die.
你在说什么?  你那边是什么声音?
What are you talking about?What's that beeping?
把对讲机给他  Danny!
Just hand her the damn walkie, Danny.
快!  现在给她!
Do it! Just do it now!
放开她
Let go of her!
Jack!
Jack?
Kate 你们有大约一个小时的时间逃走  他们不会去追你
You have about an hour head start before they come after you.
等等 你在哪里?  你在哪?
Jack, where are you?
记住我在海滩上跟你说的话吗?
You remember what I told you on the beach?
空难那天 你帮我缝针的时候  我给你讲的故事
The day of the crash?Do you remember what
story I told you when you were stitching me up?
你记得吗?
You remember it?
是的!  我记得
Yes Jack, I remember.
当你安全了 你用对讲机给我讲那个故事
When you get safe...you radio me and you tell me that story.
Jack 不要挂
Jack, please...
如果一个小时后我听不到你的声音
If don't get a call from you in the next hour
我就知道事情不对  他就死定了
I'm gonna know something went wrong,and he dies!
我不能抛下你 自己走
I can't leave without you.
- 不 你一定要这样做- Jack 我做不到
It's time, go.Jack, I can't...
- 现在就走吧- 不 我做不到
Go, now!I can't!
Kate 不要说了  快跑
Kate, damn-it, run!
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■